There's nothing wrong with the radio, just to be the station.
Which row is it in?
There's no one over there.
Looks late.
You've gotten out earlier.
Oh, look, I already lost an hour's sleep in the time chain.
I think you complained just to hear yourself talk.
There it is.
I wonder what happened to the one from last year.
Each year we spend good money on these things.
We come out here and the one from last year is gone.
Well, the flower's dying.
The caretaker or somebody takes them away.
And a little spit and polish, you can clean this up.
It's out next year.
What are how many times we bought the same one?
Hey, come on, barb church was this morning, huh?
Hey, I mean, prayers for church, huh?
Come on.
I haven't seen you in church lately.
Yeah, well.
There's not much sense in my going.
Hey, I mean, prayers for church, huh?
Come on.
I haven't seen you in church lately.
Well, there's not much sense in my going to church.
Do you remember one time when we were small, we were out here?
It was right over there.
I jumped out at you from behind the tree and grandpa got all excited.
He shook his fist at me and he said, boy, you'll be dead until hell.
Remember that? Right over there?
Well, you used to really be scared here.
Johnny.
You're still afraid.
Stop it now, I mean it.
They're coming to get you, Barbara.
Stop it. You're ignorant.
They're coming for you, Barbara.
Stop it. You're acting like a child.
They're coming for you. Look, that comes one of them now.
You hear you? Here he comes now. I'm getting out of here.
Johnny.